A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
The Library of Virginia
41597, 53598
71 cu. ft. (71 boxes)
Virginia. Dept. of Emergency Management
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 53598 transferred by the Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management, 25 Apr 22.
Biographical/Historical Information
During the 1950s and 1960s, Virginia's civil defense plan was geared toward the protection of civilian lives in the event of war and restoration of communities and industrial facilities in the event of thermonuclear war. The Emergency Services and Disaster Act of 1973 shifted the agency's focus away from nuclear disaster and toward other types of natural and man-made disasters. It repealed the 1952 act and replaced the Office of Civil Defense with the Office of Emergency Services, led by a State Coordinator of Civil Defense appointed by the Governor. The purpose of the new Office was to "insure that preparations of the State and its political subdivisions will be adequate to deal with...emergencies, and generally to provide for the common defense and to protect the public peace, health and safety, and to preserve the lives and property and economic well-being of the people of the State." Some of the duties of the State Coordinator are: prepare and maintain a State Emergency Operations Plan relating to man-made and natural disasters; coordinate and administer preparedness programs with Federal, State and local government agencies;and provide guidance and assistance to local governments in designing local emergency programs and plans. During a declared emergency operational control of this agency reverts to the Governor.
The Dept. of Emergency Management has undergone several name changes since 1973. In 1974 the agency's name was changed to State Office of Emergency Services. On 14 March 1978, Governor John N. Dalton issued an executive order assigning the functions of the State Energy Office to the State Office of Emergency Services. The agency was renamed the State Office of Emergency and Energy Services. The name was changed to Department of Emergency Services in 1985 and to Department of Emergency Management in 2000.
Today, the Virginia Department of Emergency Management works closely with local government, state and federal agencies (such as the Federal Emergency Management Agency) and voluntary organizations to provide resources and expertise in the event of a disaster. They offer disaster guidance in four areas: preparedness, response, recovery and mitigation.
Responsibility for the 911 Services Board and the Virginia Geographic Information Network Advisory Board were transferred from the Virginia Information Technologies Agency to the Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management in 2020 (HB 1003, Chap. 423, approved March 23, 2020.
Scope and Content
Correspondence and Subject Files, 1995-2013, consist of 25 boxes and are arranged in original order. These records document the planning, administrative activities, functions, major achievements and initiatives, and the implementation of agency programs, and are evidence of actions and policy decisions. Contains Chronological correspondence of the Coordinator, 2003-2013; Correspondence with the Governor's Office, 2000-2013; Correspondence with the Secretary of Public / Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, 2003-2013; Correspondence with the Federal Emergency Management Administration, 2000-2013; as well as correspondence with state and federal agencies, the National Emergency Management Association, and related subject files. Includes correspondence, budgets, decision briefs, and reports.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the original order.
Contents List
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 41597), 1987-1999.
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Jan. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Feb. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Mar. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Apr. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 May. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Jue. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 July. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Aug. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Sept. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Oct. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Nov. (Box 1)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1987 Dec. (Box 1)
  - Governor's Office: Gerald L. Baliles, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Attorney General, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Watts, Vivian E. - Secrertary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1987 Jan-June. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Watts, Vivian E. - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1987 July-Dec. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Daniel, John W., II - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Fogarty, Andrew B. - Former Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office: Gamage, Stewart H. - Virginia Liaison Office, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Code Commission, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Comptroller's Office, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Comptroller's Office - Directives, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Council on the Environment, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Emergency Medical Services, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Engineering and Buildings, Division of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Health Dept., 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: State Police, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Transportationa and Highways, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1987. (Box 2)
  - State: Water Control Board, State, 1987. (Box 2)
  - Program: Local Affairs Division, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1987 Jan-June. (Box 3)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1987 July-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Program: PDET, 1987 Jan-June. (Box 3)
  - Program: PDET, 1987 July-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Program: Regional Coordinators (I, II, III), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Program: Special Programs Division, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1987 Jan-June. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1987 July-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Dept. of Transportation (USDOT), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Dept. of Agriculture (USDA), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Army, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Dept. of Energy, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Subject: Other state agencies, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Local government, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Council of Governments (Metropolitan Washington), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: CSX Corporation, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Dupont, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA) - National Institute for Environmental Health Sciences (NIEHS) grant proposal, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Coordinating Council on Emergency Management (NCCEM), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Governors Association - Proposed policy changes, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Management Association, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company (VEPCO), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Environmental Protection Agency Pilot, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Emergency Management, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Hazard Mitigation, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Helipads (Hospitals), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Legislation, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Earthquake Hazards Reduction Program (NEHRP), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: National Institute for Environmental Health Sciences, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Proposed Rules and Regulations, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plans (RERP), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Response Team (National / Federal), 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Superfund, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: SARA, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Surry Power Station, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: VOPEX, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Almaraz Nuclear Power Plant, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Response Council, 1987. (Box 4)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Jan. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Feb. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Mar. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Apr. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 May. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 June. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 July. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Aug. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Sept. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Oct. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Nov. (Box 5)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1988 Dec. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Office: Baliles, Gerald L. - Governor, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Fogarty, Andrew - Chief of Staff, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Watts, Vivian - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1988 Jan-June. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Watts, Vivian - Secertary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1988 July-Dec. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Daniel, John W. - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Gamage, Stewart H. (Ms.) - Virginia Liaison Office, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Office: Attoney General's Office, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Conservation and Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Council on the Environment, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Emergency Management Services, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Health Dept., 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: State Library and Archives, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: State Police, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of (VDOT), 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: Water Control Board, 1988. (Box 6)
  - State: World Trade, Dept. of, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Program: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Regional Coordinators, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Local Affairs Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Program Development, Evaluation and Training Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Program: Region I - Pulaski Office, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Region II - Southwest Office, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Region II - Culpeper Office, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Special Programs Divsion, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Support Division, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Program: Wasyk, Charles - R/M and C Facility (Bellwood), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Agency for International Development, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Dept. of Agriculture (USDA), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Army, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Dept. of Energy, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Navy, 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1988 Jan-June. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1988 July-Dec. (Box 7)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Federal: Dept. of Transportation (USDOT), 1988. (Box 7)
  - Subject: Local government, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Other state agencies, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Council of Governments (Metropolitan Washington), 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Dupont, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Management Association (VEMA), 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Response Team, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Response Council, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Disaster Relief Act of 1974, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: SARA Title III, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Transportation of hazardous material, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: High level radioactive waste, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Nuclear waste transportation, 1988. (Box 8)
  - Subject: Commission on Efficiency in Government, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperation Agreement (CCA), 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: EENET Telecourse introduction, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Executive agreement, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Hazard mitigation, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials training, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 1988. (Box 9)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1988. (Box 9)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Jan. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Feb. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Mar. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Apr. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 May. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 June. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 July. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Aug. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Sept. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Oct. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Nov. (Box 10)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1989 Dec. (Box 10)
  - Program: Campell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Program Development, Evaluation and Training Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Special Programs Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Program: Support Division, 1989. (Box 10)
  - Governor's Office: Baliles, Gerald L., 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Local government, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Other state agencies, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Code Commission, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of - Office of the Comptroller, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1989. (Box 11)
  - Emergency Management Services, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Health Dept., 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: State Library, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: State Police, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of (VDOT), 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Volunteerism, Office of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1989. (Box 11)
  - State: Water Control Board, 1989. (Box 11)
  - Federal: Agency for International Development, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Dept. of Agriculture (USDA), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Army, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1989 Jan-June. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1989 July-Dec. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) - National Emergency Management Training Center, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Federal: Dept. of Transportation (USDOT), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Boy Scout Jamboree, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Emergency Management, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Flood Control Advisory Committee, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Hazard mitigation, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: HJR 162, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Legislation, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: National Governors Association, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Research alternatives, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Spill Prevention and Response Readiness Committee, 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: Virginia Military Advisory Council (VMAC), 1989. (Box 12)
  - Subject: State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Jan. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Feb. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Apr. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 May. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 June. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 July. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Aug. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Sept. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Oct. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Nov. (Box 13)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1990 Dec. (Box 13)
  - Program: Campbell, Stan - IFLOWS, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Local Affairs Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Program Development, Evaluation and Training Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Special Programs Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Program: Support Division, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Wilder, Douglas, Governor, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Shropshire, J. T. - Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Framme, Lawrence - Secretary of Economic Development, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Haskell, Elizabeth - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1987-1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1990 Jan-Mar. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1990 Apr-June. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1990 July-Sept. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1990 Oct-Dec. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Hazardous Materials Response Advisory Council - Training Study Committee, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Governor's Office: Legislative Briefing to Senate Finance Committee and House Appropriations Committee, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
  - Subject: Virginia Power, 1990. (Box 14)